One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
Prostration
Room!
Chambres!
Oh! He's been saved!
Lucy!
Underground Trading
Port Dock
Look! Nobody's up there now!
How did it go?!
What just happened?
Tell us, Gatz!
Gatz-san!
You can't yell anymore!
Don't push yourself!
You fools!
What kind of announcer am I if I can't announce the winner and the loser?
Look, you two!
Look to the sky, Dressrosa!
Which is fading?
The bird cage?
Or Doflamingo's domination?
The factory just...
The bird cage is...
The strings...
Are gone!
I can see the sky! The sky!
The sky!
I-Is the scenery outside of the cage...
a town that's been carved into pieces?
Or is it...
a land where no one will manipulate us anymore - a land of freedom?
The bird cage's gone!
That means...
The "Great Defense of Dressrosa"!
The two thousand pirates of the Donquixote Family...
versus
the fated warriors, here by coincidence!
And the duel between their leaders!
Royal Warlord of the Sea, Donquixote Doflamingo...
versus
the gladiator, Lucy!
Dah winnah...
What?
What's he saying?
It's "the winner"!
Dah winnah ish...
You can do it, Gatz-san!
Dah winnah...
Stay with us, Gatz!
Who's there?!
Don't shout. Don't call for anyone.
I am Donquixote Doflamingo.
I am the rightful king of this kingdom.
The king has returned!
Is it something we did?
There is no excuse for this.
The country is done for!
This was Doflamingo's trap!
Dah winnah...
Get a grip already!
Speak clearly!
Listen, Rebecca.
Don't cry yet.
I won't let the soldier die.
Make sure you stay safe.
I'm gonna beat the crap outta Doflamingo!
Lucy...
The winner is...
...Lucy!
Lucy!
Thank you, Lucy!
This is the best!
He did it!
Super!
Luffyland!
Luffy!
Robiland!
He finally did it!
Well done, my boy!
Truly incredible!
Expect nothing less of Luffy-dono!
Princess!
I'm so glad!
Fraland!
All of you did great, too!
You're hurting us!
We toys were once human!
Captain!
They will fight alongside us.
They are the dwarfs of the Tontatta Kingdom.
Are you really sure about leaving her?
She was crying!
Even toys have something they want to protect!
Although these tin eyes of mine cannot shed tears.
That's why the captain has been fighting on his own for ten years.
What have you done to this country and the king, pirate?!
The king set the city ablaze.
Didn't you see him?
His Majesty would never do such a thing!
This battle is to restore the honor of King Riku who was dethroned in shame ten years ago,
and to regain our freedom!
Soldier-san!
I will not let you take...
another member of my family from me!
A country in ruins needn't necessarily be unhappy.
On this day, amid piles of rubble, the people of this very country...
cried out in joy.
Hooray!
Doflamingo was taken down!
We're free from now on!
Mom! Dad!
Thank God!
Gatz-san!
Yeah, he did it!
So aren't you gonna finish me off?
Don't need to.
Seems like it's all over.
You brothers are too soft!
After losing to our captain at Banaro Island,
Ace had something to say
before he was handed over to the Navy.
Wanna hear it?
Underground Port
Hey, hurry up!
The duel between Straw Hat and Doflamingo is over!
The Navy'll be here soon!
We know!
You call the chief yet?
We're trying!
He's not picking up.
He only answers when he feels like it.
You'll get a kick outta hearin' it!
He realized he was gonna be executed, so he said...
Don't tell my brother.
Man, what an idiot!
He had no idea how much he was worth!
If Fire Fist Ace was captured by the Navy,
the news would spread all over the world!
The Navy would make 120% use of his pathetic life-
That's quite enough.
Stop talking.
How he felt when he passed away...
Fire Fist Ace Dies
I've thought about it non-stop
since that day, every single night.
You don't have to tell me. I fully understand!
Then let it sink in, fool!
As for that Devil Fruit you have...
If I can't steal it here, it'll damage
my reputation as a hunter of Devil Fruit users.
You're not getting away from me, Flame Fruit!
You're regretting it, aren't you?!
Even though you had the title and the power,
you still didn't try to save your brother!
You weren't there at all, were you?!
Were you taking a nap or something?
You weren't there when he needed you most.
And you call yourselves brothers!
I'm done regretting it!
Fire Fist!
Dammit!
I've made peace with it,
but Ace is saying he can't forgive you.
Oh! Hello, Sabo-kun?
Where in the world are you?!
I saw Burgess going after Luffy-kun earlier,
so I frantically tried to contact you, but you weren't answering at all!
That so? I wasn't paying attention.
You weren't what?!
Don't worry, I took care of it already.
That aside, Koala, have you found the list?
For crying out... Yes, I found it!
Then just call the ship and-
I called it!
Well, let's meet up with Hack underground then.
I'm with Hack and everyone else underground!
Why did he hang up?! That selfish jerk!
Stop taking it out on me, Koala-san!
There he is!
The Donquixote Family!
Their eight commanders and...
...three top commanders are all accounted for!
Watch out!
Most of the commanders are Devil Fruit users!
Secure them with Sea Stone!
Yes, sir!
Just stay here with me.
Yes.
Whoa! Wh-What're you doing?!
You said, "Stay here with me"!
So we'll be together forever!
Get off of me!
Have we contacted Navy HQ yet?
Well, actually...
Isshou-san said, "Don't file a report yet."
Vice Admiral Maynard!
The Surveillance Snail is ready!
Alright, I'll do the talking.
Take another Surveillance Snail
and follow Isshou-san, per orders!
Yes, sir!
Applenine - A Neighboring Country
This is Applenine Island, a country near Dressrosa.
What the heck?
What's wrong?
I heard there'll be a broadcast from Dressrosa!
Will it be a speech from King Doflamingo?
Scary, isn't it?
This is Dressrosa...
Another Neighboring Country
We are broadcasting to the three neighboring island countries within range of the Surveillance Snail.
Yet Another Neighboring Country
I am Navy HQ Vice Admiral Maynard!
The Navy?
This is Dressrosa.
We are broadcasting to the three neighboring island countries within range of the Surveillance Snail.
But why?
I want you to take a look at these images!
What's up with the piles of rubble?
What you're seeing is
the current state of Dressrosa!
What does he mean?
I ask you to keep calm as I tell you...
all the details of what the Warlord,
Donquixote Doflamingo, did today in this very country!
Isshou-san, I'll do as you asked.
We're begging you, Your Majesty!
So many of us citizens were turned into toys and couldn't speak out!
No! Please... stop this.
Even if the misunderstanding about me has cleared up,
I cannot return as your king.
No! You are this country's true king!
That's right!
We're sick and tired of violence!
Your Majesty!
What if everyone in the kingdom shared your values?
Wait.
The Riku Family's position falls apart when faced with turmoil.
This event has proven that.
We don't care if we fall to ruin!
We'd gladly fall to ruin if there were
any hope for peace together with you!
We want you to renounce war, as our pacifist king!
That's right!
Even if it causes our country to fall, we're fine with that!
We don't mind being poor!
Just make Dressrosa a peaceful country again!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, we're begging you!
As a fighting king, their words grate my ears!
Elizabello!
Your Majesty! You must return to the palace at once!
Kings from neighboring countries keep calling us!
What did you say?
I had to tell them right away...
that King Riku is coming back.
They were all overjoyed to hear that!
The King of Prodence!
It's barely been a decade.
How could you age so much?
Where is the man who would stare down the world to avoid a war?
Your people are waiting for you.
Come home...
Miracle King, Riku Dold!
He is right, King Riku!
All this trouble that Doflamingo caused...
I would rather you not take responsibility for it.
That vicious pirate was approved as king of a country
under the Seven Warlords system,
and thus permitted to reign over this island by none other than...
the World Government!
To all who inhabit this country...
and to all members of its royal family...
On behalf of the Government,
I most humbly apologize!
We most deeply regret what has been done!
What are you...
The Navy admiral has prostrated himself?
You're kidding me...
The Government controls the Navy!
And one of the Navy admirals,
the greatest of their military might...
is bowing before King Riku and his nation in apology!
What the heck is going on in Dressrosa?
Law - Straw Hat Pirate Alliance
That pirate alliance took down
the Celestial Yaksha, Doflamingo?
Take pictures! Put them in print already!
This is completely unheard of!
The false glory of the mighty country, Dressrosa, and the truth behind it.
The downfall of the world's greatest
underground broker, Doflamingo.
And the prostration of Navy HQ Admiral Fujitora.
The major incidents that were confined within the cage...
have just been released to the entire world.
An admiral from
Navy HQ has prostrated himself?!
The Surveillance Snail is running, too!
Th-That's a Navy admiral, isn't it?
Wh-What happened?
Something's going on in Dressrosa!
Raise your head, Fujitora.
Fujitora, aren't you worried about the world seeing this?
You couldn't possibly...
Could it be...
that you stayed away from Doflamingo so you could enact this?
Fujitora!
The world must know the truth!
I left all the fighting to them.
I made a wager on them.
We are the ones who allowed the Warlords to do as they please.
So who are we to point our swords at them,
and yet preach about justice without bearing shame?
This country earned its victory at the hands of pirates, warriors, and its citizens!
Our long, hard battle is at last over.
I am truly...
I am truly grateful for your hard work.
Little Army of King Riku, Special Anti-Doflamingo Forces!
Yes, Commander!
As of today, you are all...
...dismissed!
Commander!
Tank!
The Navy still has their position to consider.
Hide the pirates and warriors
who fought for us in the palace.
Take those without shelter there as well.
I hate to ask, but can I count on you?
Of course, it would be my pleasure, Your Majesty!
The Red Line
Holy Land, Mariejois
So...
Reporting Doflamingo's resignation, and then revealing it as false...
Was this all by order of those people above you?
World Government Supreme Authority
The Five Elder Stars
Navy Headquarters Fleet Admiral
Sakazuki (Akainu)
Why should the world be deceived
for the sake of someone like Doflamingo?!
If something like this ever happens again,
it'll bring shame on me as fleet admiral!
Don't ever do that again, under any circumstances!
Don't give us any of your cheek, Sakazuki.
Your honor is completely inconsequential.
The Navy is merely the public face of the Government.
We left this case entirely up to Cipher Pol.
Hmph! Cipher Pol, huh?
So simply put,
they've gone over your heads.
Those damn puppets of the Celestial Dragons!
Watch your mouth, Sakazuki!
And what of Kuzan's actions?
I can hardly believe a powerful man like him
sides with Blackbeard now.
That is sure to bring dishonor to the Navy!
That idiot resigned from the Navy!
Where he is and what he's doing is not our responsibility!
Five Elder Stars! Fleet Admiral Sakazuki!
Reporting in!
The Warlord, Donquixote Doflamingo, and his family
were defeated by the Law - Straw Hat Pirate Alliance.
And Dressrosa has been destroyed.
There's nothing left of it!
What'd you say?!
Again...
...with that brat?
And there's one more thing...
Countries Across the New World
The video and story that were sent to Dressrosa's neighbors spread from one island to the next.
Extra! Extra!
The news spread like wildfire
throughout the world, with dire repercussions.
Doflamingo Falls!!
Joker was defeated!
Your Majesty!
We have no other way to acquire weapons!
Announce our surrender.
The war is over!
We've already paid! We had a deal!
That bastard, Joker!
I know they still have weapons in Dressrosa!
Don't! There's still a Navy admiral over there!
Our deal for the Devil Fruits!
What'll happen to the Smiles deal now?!
If only these fools weren't there!
Come now, Tsuru-chan!
You didn't need to tag along with us!
I ought to be saying that, Inspector General!
Well, they're the pirate group that you've been chasing after all this time, aren't they?
Yes, under your orders.
Want some rice crackers?
In a Certain Town
How's this? This is today's special mixed pizza.
Huh? Thief!
Hey, old lady! Stop!
Crap, where did she go?
Tsk, just a little girl. Old lady, where'd you go?!
Oh, they took down Doflamingo.
Not bad.
Makes me happy to be from the same generation.
From South Blue - Captain of the Bonney Pirates
"The Glutton" Jewelry Bonney
In a certain sky
High Priest Urouge!
Th-There's somebody here! High Priest!
From the Sky Islands - Captain of the Fallen Monk Pirates
"Mad Monk" Urouge
Nonsense! We're on a Sky Island.
It's an abandoned and isolated cloud island, at that.
Nobody but us could possibly-
In a certain sea
Whoa, whoa, not bad, that pirate alliance.
Looks like my fellow pirates ain't doing too shabby.
From West Blue - Captain of the Fire Tank Pirates
Capone "Gang" Bege
Capture Caesar at any cost, boys!
Yes, Father!
The Kid Pirates' Hideout
They made their move before we knew it.
It's a huge victory!
Doflamingo is connected to Kaidou behind the scenes, for sure.
Well, that's gonna make Kaidou pretty mad, yeah?
From South Blue - Captain of the Kid Pirates
Eustass "Captain" Kid
If they planned this, their target must be...
From North Blue - Captain of the Hawkins Pirates
"The Mage" Basil Hawkins
...one of the Four Emperors, as we thought.
From the Grand Line (Longarm Tribe) - Captain of the On-Air Pirates
"Roaring Tide" Scratchmen Apoo
"Beast King" Kaidou, eh?
From South Blue - Kid Pirates Combatant
"Soldier of Slaughter" Killer
Good thing our target isn't theirs.
We won't have to fight each other
and waste our military might.
Our target is one of the other Four Emperors,
"Red Hair" Shanks!
And now we shift attention to Drake,
who once provoked a battle in Kaidou's territory...
A Certain Island
Your father was killed? By Doflamingo?
That was a long time ago. I bear no grudge.
From North Blue - Captain of the Drake Pirates
"Red Flag" X-Drake
What gives? That's pretty heartless of you.
Hey, give us a hand here!
This is an emergency!
If we don't let him know right away, he'll snap!
Kaidou-sama! Where are you?
That idiot Joker screwed up big time!
We won't be receiving Smiles anymore!
Don't play dumb with me, Isshou!
Dressrosa
You know full well the gravity of
a Navy admiral admitting to oversight!
Why didn't you report to HQ first?!
Had I reported in, surely you would have changed
the details of the report yet again, would you not?
What did you just say?!
I also feel the Seven Warlord system must end.
Two years ago, I was there when Crocodile showed his true nature.
The Navy couldn't do anything!
If it weren't for the Straw Hats,
Alabasta would be another country
governed by a pirate, just like Dressrosa.
Yet the Government reported that it was the Navy's doing!
If only I held higher rank then!
I can't believe Fujitora really did it.
It reminds me of the frustration I felt
at Alabasta Kingdom two years ago.
The Straw Hats' triumph was covered up then.
It's like he paid them back for us.
Even if I held the same rank as him,
I couldn't have pulled that off.
I could feast on this feeling for days.
Oh, we have muffins! How about some coffee?
That didn't mean I wanted to eat, you idiot!
Hey lady, I'm hungry!
We're hungry too!
We have muffins! How about some coffee?
You can't give kids coffee!
I want a muffin!
Are we at Megapants' yet?
That's "Vegapunk".
It'll be a few more days until we reach Dr. Vegapunk's lab.
How lovely!
Captain-chan's sweet to the kids!
I wish I were a kid!
Hey, you bunch!
There's still tons of work to do!
Aye aye, ma'am!
Scold me more, Captain-chan!
Cover-ups happen all the time!
I would rather not be a hero forged upon lies.
It was our employer, the World Government,
that hired pirates to maintain balance in the world.
This is a matter of the Navy's credibility and dignity!
I-Isshou-san, y-you're talking to...
Your selfish actions dishonor the very name of justice!
If you value your justice so damn much,
then keep a close eye on it!
If we lose credibility just for admitting fault,
we haven't any in the first place!
Then you clean up after yourself, Fujitora!
Straw Hat and Law... Until you bring me their heads,
you are hereby barred from setting foot within any Navy base in the world!
Good, that's exactly what I wanted to hear.
Meat...